// Creating an array and passing the number,question and answers

let questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "What is the capital of Nigeria?",
        answer: "Abuja",
        options: [
            "Lagos",
            "Port-Harcourt",
            "Calabar",
            "Abuja",
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 2,
        question: "What does HTML stands for?",
        answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Hyper Text Makeup Languege",
            "Hyper Test Markup Language",
            "Hypper Text markup Language",
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 3,
        question: "What does CSS stands for?",
        answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
        options: [
            "Cascading Style Sheet",
            "Cacading Style Sheet",
            "Casceding Styling Sheet",
            "Cascading Style Shete",
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 4,
        question: "What does SQL stands for?",
        answer: "Structured Query Language",
        options: [
            "Structured Quary Language",
            "Structured Query Linguage",
            "Structure Query Language",
            "Structured Query Language",
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 5,
        question: "A line that divide a circle into two equal parts is called?",
        answer: "diameter",
        options: [
            "sector",
            "chord",
            "diameter",
            "radius",
        ]
    },
    // {
    //     number: 6,
    //     question: "A sachet of pure water cost #1.00,if 20 sachets bought at once would be given for #150,how much is saved on hundred sachet bought?",
    //     answer: "#250",
    //     options: [
    //         "#150",
    //         "#250",
    //         "#200",
    //         "#350",
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     number: 7,
    //     question: "How many geopolitical zones is nigeria divided into?",
    //     answer: "Six",
    //     options: [
    //         "Eight",
    //         "Five",
    //         "Four",
    //         "Six",
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     number: 8,
    //     question: "A nucleus has a mass number of 12 and an atomic number of 6.What is the number of neutrons in the nucleus?",
    //     answer: "Six",
    //     options: [
    //         "Eight",
    //         "Five",
    //         "Four",
    //         "Six",
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     number: 9,
    //     question: "What is S.I unit of inductance?",
    //     answer: "Henry",
    //     options: [
    //         "Farads",
    //         "Henry",
    //         "Joule",
    //         "Newton",
    //     ]
    // },

    // {
    //     number: 6,
    //     question: "What is the process called when plants make their own food?",
    //     answer: "Photosynthesis",
    //     options: [
    //         "Digestion",
    //         "Photosynthesis",
    //         "Excretion",
    //         "Reproduction",
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     number: 7,
    //     question: "What is the capital of Nigeria?",
    //     answer: "Abuja",
    //     options: [
    //         "Lagos",
    //         "Port-Harcourt",
    //         "Calabar",
    //         "Abuja",
    //     ]
    // },




]